http://800newbride.com/terms-of-use/

Refund Policy
Full-price products are returnable within 30 days of purchase as long as they are in unused condition. Return by mail to the address belowRegarding sale items, all purchases are final.
Risk of Loss
Items purchased from 1-800-New-Bride are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
THIS SITE IS PROVIDED BY BRIDAL MARKETING SERVICES, LC ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS.
1-800-NEW-BRIDE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE OPERATION OF THIS SITE OR THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, OR PRODUCTS INCLUDED ON THIS SITE. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THIS SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY APPLICABLE LAW,
BRIDAL MARKETING SERVICES, LC DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
Our Mailing Address:
Bridal Marketing Services, LC1795 Williston Road, Suite 200South Burlington, VT 05403http://www.800newbride.com
Privacy Policy
Bridal Marketing Services, LC respects the privacy of its users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We are particularly sensitive to the protection of your credit card and personal information.
Privacy Protection
We use secure server technology (SSL) to transmit your information in an encrypted format. The secure certificate that enables this comes from Thawte, a premier provider of Internet security technology. This ensures the safety of your credit card and other information. We are careful to assure the privacy of your information throughout our order processing and record maintenance systems.
Personal Information
We
do not collect personal information about you unless you specifically
provide this information to 1-800-New-Bride on a voluntary basis.
Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our
business partners. We will not use your personal information to send
you promotional offers unless you “opt-in” to receive such
offers.
If you have any questions regarding the 1-800-New-Bride privacy policy, please contact us at info@800response.com.
